<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cowntdown</string>
    <!-- home screen -->
    <string name="description_introduction">Cowntdown was created to keep the \"wake-up\" trend alive and make countdowns more engaging. Built using Jetpack Compose and following Clean Architecture, the app ensures a smooth user experience while maintaining scalability.</string>
    <string name="worker_notification">Worker Notifications – Sends reminders even when the app is closed.</string>
    <string name="intuitive_navigation">Intuitive Navigation – Simplified user flow using Navigation Compose.</string>
    <string name="modern_ui">Modern UI – Designed with Material 3, featuring a customizable theme.</string>

    <!-- fun fact screen -->
    <string name="fun_fact_1">Cows have best friends and get stressed when separated from them.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_2">Cows can recognize faces and remember them for years.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_3">A cow\'s moo can be heard up to 6 miles away on a clear day.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_4">Cows have 32 teeth, but they don\'t have upper front teeth.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_5">Cows sleep standing up but lie down to rest deeply.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_6">A cow\'s stomach has four compartments to help digest food.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_7">Cows spend about 8 hours a day eating.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_8">Cows can walk up to 5 miles per hour when they are motivated.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_9">Cows are herbivores, meaning they only eat plants.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_10">The average cow produces about 6.3 gallons of milk every day.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_11">Cows can be as intelligent as dogs, and some can even learn to fetch things.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_12">A cow can weigh between 1,000 to 1,800 pounds on average.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_13">Cows can live up to 20 years or more with proper care.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_14">Cows communicate with each other using a variety of vocalizations, body language, and facial expressions.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_15">A cow\'s sense of smell is 10 times stronger than a human\'s.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_16">Cows can be trained to use a leash like dogs.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_17">In Hinduism, cows are considered sacred animals.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_18">Cows have panoramic vision and can see 360 degrees around them.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_19">Cows spend 50% of their day chewing cud, which is partially digested food that they regurgitate.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_20">Cows have a keen sense of direction and can find their way home from miles away.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_21">Cows\' milk is used to make more than just dairy products—it\'s also used in soaps and lotions.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_22">Cows are social animals and enjoy the company of other cows.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_23">There are over 900 different breeds of cows in the world.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_24">Cows produce methane, a potent greenhouse gas, from digestion, which contributes to global warming.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_25">The longest recorded lifespan of a cow was 48 years.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_26">A cow\'s tongue is so strong it can curl around grass and pull it into its mouth.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_27">Cows are sensitive to sound and will often respond to certain music.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_28">Cows are known to have a great memory, able to remember faces and places for years.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_29">The average cow produces 2.5 times its body weight in milk every year.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_30">The world record for the largest milk-producing cow is 74.5 pounds of milk per day.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_31">Cows can see color, but their vision is different from humans; they see shades of red and blue better than other colors.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_32">Cows are ruminants, meaning they regurgitate food from their stomach to chew it again.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_33">A cow\'s udders can hold up to 25 liters of milk at a time.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_34">Cows\' hooves are tough and can support the weight of the animal without any problems.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_35">Cows have been domesticated for over 10,000 years.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_36">The average cow can produce around 350,000 glasses of milk in its lifetime.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_37">Cows like to be brushed, and some can be trained to enjoy a good back scratch.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_38">The tallest cow ever recorded stood at 6 feet 4 inches tall.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_39">Cows are gentle animals that tend to form deep bonds with each other.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_40">Cows\' milk contains about 87% water, which helps keep them hydrated.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_41">A group of cows is called a herd.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_42">Cows are excellent swimmers and can even swim across rivers if needed.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_43">Cows have a very strong sense of hearing, and they can hear frequencies up to 23,000 Hz.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_44">Cows are herbivores and mainly graze on grass, but they also eat other plants like clover and hay.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_45">Cows can walk in a straight line, but if you try to confuse them, they will start walking in circles.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_46">Cows can give birth to twins, although it is rare.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_47">Cows are used to help maintain ecosystems by grazing on vegetation, which helps prevent wildfires.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_48">Cows have been shown to be able to solve simple puzzles when motivated with food.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_49">Cows\' eyes are located on the sides of their heads, which allows them to see predators from a distance.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_50">Cows can walk up to 2 miles per hour when they are calm.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_51">Cows have a very good sense of smell, and they can detect odors from up to 5 miles away.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_52">Cows are often depicted as lazy, but they can be quite active, especially when they are playing or interacting with other cows.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_53">Cows can form strong emotional bonds with humans and can recognize their caretakers.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_54">The average dairy cow weighs around 1,200 pounds (545 kg).</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_55">Cows are often trained to respond to their names and can recognize the voice of their owner.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_56">The milk produced by cows contains over 200 different components, including vitamins, minerals, proteins, and fat.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_57">Cows communicate with their owners using body language and vocalizations, just like other animals.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_58">The heaviest cow ever recorded weighed 3,000 pounds (1,360 kg).</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_59">Cows are often seen as a symbol of fertility and abundance in many cultures.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_60">A cow\'s stomach has four compartments: the rumen, reticulum, omasum, and abomasum.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_61">Cows have a large, sensitive nose that helps them find food, water, and even detect danger.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_62">Cows are sometimes given names based on their personalities or markings.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_63">Cows can express a wide range of emotions, from happiness and contentment to frustration and fear.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_64">Cows are one of the most important sources of food for humans, providing milk, cheese, butter, and meat.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_65">Cows are very social creatures and can develop deep friendships with other cows.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_66">Cows have a very strong maternal instinct and will fiercely protect their calves.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_67">Cows are often used in therapy programs because of their calm and peaceful nature.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_68">The fastest cow can run up to 20 miles per hour (32 km/h).</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_69">Cows produce milk for a full year after giving birth, even if they are not continuously pregnant.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_70">Cows are creatures of habit and prefer to follow a consistent routine.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_71">The average cow produces about 150,000 glasses of milk over its lifetime.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_72">Cows have been domesticated for thousands of years, providing essential resources for human civilization.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_73">Cows are capable of walking over 6 miles (10 km) a day in search of food.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_74">Cows\' milk is rich in calcium, which is important for bone health.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_75">Cows love to be outside in the sunshine and will often seek shade when it gets too hot.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_76">Some cows can be trained to pull carts or wagons, similar to horses.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_77">Cows\' eyes have an excellent range of vision, allowing them to see in almost all directions at once.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_78">Cows can produce milk with different fat content, ranging from low-fat to full-fat milk.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_79">Cows have an amazing sense of balance and can even stand on uneven terrain.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_80">Cows can be trained to walk on a leash like dogs and even go on walks with their owners.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_81">Cows\' milk is used to create a wide range of dairy products, including cheese, butter, and yogurt.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_82">Cows are sometimes used to help graze and control unwanted vegetation in areas such as parks or golf courses.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_83">Cows love to be brushed and enjoy being pampered by their caretakers.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_84">Some cows have unique coat patterns, with patches of different colors and shapes.</string>
    <string name="fun_fact_85">Cows are capable of forming complex relationships with other animals, including humans, dogs, and even cats.</string>
</resources>